import React from 'react'
let secret = {
    title: "Secret Identities",
    questions: [
        {
            question: "Clark Kent is the secret identity of this superhero.",
            answers: ["Black Adam", "Superman", "Wolverine", "Antman"],
            correct: "Superman"
        },
        {
            question: "Bruce Wayne is the secret identity of this superhero",
            answers: ["Batman", "Robin", "Aquaman", "Daredevil"],
            correct: "Batman"
        },
        {
            question: "Matt Murdock is the secret identity of this superhero",
            answers: ["The Flash", "Daredevil", "Green Arrow",  "Iron Man"],
            correct: "Daredevil"
        },
        {
            question: "Billy Batson is the secret identity of this superhero",
            answers: ["Superman","Green Arrow","Shazam", "Black Adam"],
            correct: "Shazam"
        },
        {
            question: "Carol Danvers is the secret identity of this superhero",
            answers: ["Batwoman", "Dark Phoenix", "She-Hulk", "Captain Marvel"],
            correct: "Captain Marvel"
        },
        {
            question: "Diana Prince is the secret identity of this superhero",
            answers: ["Wonder Woman", "Captain Marvel", "Wasp", "Mystique"],
            correct: "Wonder Woman"
        },
        {
            question: "Faith Herbert is the secret identity of this superhero",
            answers: ["Witchblade","Zephyr", "Rocket", "Mystique"],
            correct: "Zephyr"
        },
        {
            question: "Hal Jordan is the secret identity of this superhero",
            answers: ["Thor","Green Lantern", "Green Arrow", "Batman"],
            correct: "Green Lantern"
        }, {
            question: "Reed Richards is the secret identity of this superhero",
            answers: ["Stretch", "Mr. Fantastic", "Nightwing", "Azrael"],
            correct: "Mr. Fantastic"
        },
        {
            question: "Dinah Drake is the secret identity of this superhero",
            answers: ["Nightwing", "Witchblade", "Black Canary","Mystique"],
            correct: "Black Canary"
        }
    ]
}

export default secret